Goto Ryuji's not fighting.
Still, it's thanks to him that I get
to watch S-Rank hunters do battle.
Well...
Let's get started!
A test of strength, huh?
I appreciate the simplicity!
But which of us is stronger?!
So fast! I'm at a disadvantage
in close-quarters combat!
My specialty is ranged attacks!
Hoshino! Watch it!
Hurry and take him down already!
Chairman, this building's been reinforced with
the highest quality of essence stone, yes?
It has.
That said, we might need to reevaluate
how durable it actually is.
These guys are the cream of the crop
among S-Rank hunters.
I need to move like they're trying to snap
my wrists, not just grab them!
I think this one's name was Kumamoto Atsushi.
He doesn't seem very aggressive.
Damn it. I'm not cut out for this at all.
I guess I just don't have the heart for it.
The idea might be to use us to test him.
To make sure he's prepared to fight the ants.
So I'm supposed to be a test, huh...
Time to see if you pass or fail!
Oh, crap! I just can't!
Whatta buncha maniacs.
My little A-Ranked self
wouldn't stand a chance.
That's just not true!
You're plenty strong yourself, Master!
I guess I won the test of strength.
You drove me into the ground!
That's honestly a first.
Looks like I win.
Are you just going to keep runn—
Do I seem weaker than Hunter Cha?
That's kind of insulting...
I can't predict her next move!
The Dancer, Cha Hae-in...
Seeing her fight in person really
drives home how accurate the name is!
Tag.
I had better help Hunter Baek.
What was that?!
Oh, no, I lashed out on reflex!
Aw, hell, he's snapped.
There's no telling what he'll do now.
Should we stop him?
Only if it looks like
someone's gonna get injured.
So fast!
That looks bad!
Maybe it's none of my business,
but this doesn't feel like
friendly sparring anymore.
Who the hell are you?!
No way... He was able to just brush off
Kumamoto, even in his berserk state!
And this is the hunter that's
supposed to be a mage type?
That's what I heard, yes.
Guess I'll have to find out for myself.
Hunter Cha, you're willing
to accept the loss, yes?
Considering Hunter Baek seems
to have already dropped out.
Right.
Even if I'd gone all out, it wouldn't have
been enough to turn things around.
Hunter Sung.
Guildmaster Goto is asking
if you'd like to spar with him.
His body is radiating fighting spirit...
He probably wants to see what I've got.
This'll be a good chance to test the power
I gained from the Demon's Castle.
Did he just smile?
At the thought of facing me?
Hunter Sung has accepted your challenge, sir.
But he has a stipulation.
What's that?
He'll agree to spar on the condition
that you hold nothing back.
Interesting.
The fourth Jeju Island raid is approaching.
After the formation of an alliance with Japan,
preparations are now underway
to ensure a successful outcome.
Do you got work today?
I'm off. I told ya yesterday.
You did?
Well, the hunters are workin' hard,
so we better do our best, too.
Hello. Well...
I had some questions about
the Jeju raid's defensive forces.
What's going on now?
So this is the famous tenth S-Rank.
He's a feisty one to wanna take on Goto!
I saw him fight in an A-Rank dungeon before,
but will he be okay against an S-Rank hunter?
You don't seem to mind being
around other hunters today.
It's not like I can be constantly
covering my nose on the battlefield.
Should we stop them?
It's a melee hunter going up against
a spellcaster in close combat...
Normally, I would.
But I'm thinking the same thing
you are, Hunter Cha.
Can't help but get your hopes up, right?
If my suspicion is right,
and Hunter Sung is an awakened with
the power to continue growing stronger...
Well, let's—
Come on, man, I wasn't finished.
His speed and agility...
And he's a mage type? What a joke.
Let's see who you really are!
He's definitely a step above
the other S-Ranks.
But he's not so fast that I can't dodge him.
Smiling again...?
The attacks are so fast,
I can't even follow them.
He's doing a great job evading.
And that's a real accomplishment
with attacks like that.
He's not just dodging, either.
He's testing his opponent's strength.
The idea of him running circles around me
is getting on my nerves.
Change of plans.
I'll crush him for real!
Hunter Sung!
Careful, now. Someone could've lost an eye.
He grabbed my hand instead of my wrist.
Are you toying with me?
I'm not sure what you're saying, but...
If I had grabbed your wrist,
the game would've been over.
And I doubt either of us
want it to end that easily.
Whoa, Goto's getting serious!
If they keep going, both of them
could end up seriously injured!
Ice?
Hunter Sung!
Goto!
Let's call it off. If this keeps up,
it's going to get out of control!
Tell him to stop sparring!
R-Right!
Did I spoil your fun?
Not at all.
You fought the mighty Goto, and it only
cost you a scratch! You're pretty good.
I got a little hot under the collar. But...
Now I've got a good grasp
on the skills of everyone here.
I was able to send soldiers
into five of their shadows, too.
I'll be sending the information on the
hunters involved in the raid later.
If you could forward them to our
vice guild master too, please.
Of course.
Chairman Go.
What is it, Hunter Sung?
About the Jeju Island raid...
Reiji. One of the hunters
over here is pretty good.
I doubt he's a real match for the
Drawn Sword's guild master, though.
Don't be too sure about that.
Which one is it?
Sung Jinwoo. He's a reawakened
who recently became S-Rank.
That's strange.
I don't see his name on
the roster for the raid.
What?
Hunter Sung isn't accompanying us
on the raid, I see.
I'm sure he's got his reasons.
That said...
Byung-gu's name isn't here, either.
Still...
We've already got 15 S-Rank hunters.
I'm sure that this time...
We're going to win!
I'm home.
You're late, Jinwoo!
Welcome home, Jinwoo.
Dinner's ready.
Good to be back.
Mom just woke up from a four-year coma.
She needs my help.
Which is why...
I'm not going to Jeju Island.
With the lack of new prey,
they've begun to cannibalize each other.
There is not enough food here
for my subjects to feast on.
This won't do.
We must leave this island.
I need stronger offspring...
A child more powerful than any other,
capable of leading our kingdom.
Grow strong, my son.
The ant magic beasts have been
evolving at a disturbing rate.
Though they crawled along the ground
during the third Jeju Island raid,
as you can see in this
recently captured footage,
they've taken a more humanoid appearance
in addition to growing
large wings on their backs.
The Hunter's Association has begun formulating
a strategy for dealing with
these latest beasts in response.
There you are, magic beast!
Now you have to face an S-Rank hunter!
This is a bad idea! It's way too dangerous.
Why shouldn't I join the defense force?
Well, Ms. Han, you're an E-Rank, for one...
So that's how it's gonna be?!
Ow, ow, ow! Sorry!
As a countermeasure against even a single ant
making it to the mainland,
hunters are being enlisted to defensive duty.
Tomorrow's the day...
of the Jeju Island raid.
This is the first fleet.
We've arrived at our destination
in the vicinity of Jeju Island.
Second fleet reporting. We have arrived.
This is the third fleet.
We're approaching the perimeter.
Fourth fleet here. We're en route.
We anticipate arrival in five minutes.
Master, do you think we're
strong enough to fight the ants?
No way to know until ya try.
But we've been sent out here
in case of an emergency.
Gotta keep those creepy-crawlies
from reachin' the mainland.
You're amazing, Master!
I'll follow you for the rest of my life!
Take care of things for me.
I doubt it'll come to that.
Probably gonna spend the day spacing out...
You can never be sure!
Besides, having my vice
guild master at the ready
means I can rest easy
when I head into battle.
Just be careful, sir.
Will do.
Why in the hell is Minsung
positioned all the way up here?!
It's gonna be bad news if things pop off!
Send him further back!
The teams have all made contact.
Both the mainland coastal guard
and Jeju Island hunters are ready.
The diversionary force has successfully
landed on the island.
A large number of hunters
heard the call of duty this time.
And it's a relief that he
decided to join, as well.
Byung-gu!
I didn't think you'd come.
I realized you'd probably be dead in seconds
without a healer watching your back.
You charge straight in when
you see magic beasts, y'know?
Only because if I didn't,
they'd probably kill you!
This is the city
at the center of the island.
Alpha here. All hunters, sound off.
Bravo here, in position.
Charlie, in position.
Delta, ready for action.
A live broadcast?
Right. Well, with a ten-minute delay
in case of any accidents.
As a cameraman for the hunter
communications department,
I'll make sure to document
this battle for the people!
A hunter can really go all-out when
they've got something to protect!
That said, this is going to be pretty intense.
Are you gonna be okay?
Don't worry. Funnily enough, I'm an A-Rank.
I'm used to filming in hazardous conditions.
Good to know.
This might be the last chance the public
ever gets to watch an S-Rank raid.
Hell, it had better be.
Because this time,
we're going to finish it for good!
If we don't pull this off, our whole country
could be wiped off the map.
We need a hero.
The strike team is prepared to mobilize.
Then let the fourth Jeju Island raid commence!
All hunters, release your full strength!
Roger!
The diversionary force is making their move.
What incredible magic power.
And there go the ants.
Whoa, we've got some headed our way, too!
Please open the hatch.
I'll handle it.
Incredible...
There are quite a few of them.
I'm afraid I'll have to get a bit more rough.
After all this time, I'm finally back.
Back on this island.
That's the ultimate weapon for you!
Glad he's here.
Well, everyone, let's touch down.
The Japanese hunters should be able
to distract the ants for about an hour.
Which means that's our deadline
for taking down the queen.
Everybody ready?
We can do this!
Let's go!
We're ready to get started, too.
Start up the interference signal.
Initiating signal interference.
Now the ants won't be able to detect
the queen's distress signal.
Kumamoto! If you keep flinching,
you're gonna die!
Wouldn't it be faster for us
to just kill all the ants
instead of waiting for the others
to get the queen?
Possibly. Where's Kenzo?
Goofing around over there. He's like a kid.
Did you see that flame?
It's gotta be that Choi guy, right?
If he and I fought,
do you think I could take him?
I run hot and cold on the subject.
The nest is contained. We should keep
moving while the distraction is effective.
This sure is a lot of tunnels, though.
How are we supposed to find
the one that leads to the queen?
What the hell was that?! Be careful!
We don't have the time to search them all.
We just need to find the one that leads
the deepest underground, right?
I believe it's that one.
That's today's daily quest done.
No one around today, either.
All of the S-Rank hunters
on this raid are strong.
They should be able to handle it easily.
Even without me.
And the queen is really down here?
Maybe she abandoned them to run.
It's an island.
There's nowhere for her to go.
Everyone, take a look at this.
It's an egg chamber!
The queen's room should be nearby.
Look there!
That egg...
No way... That's an ant egg?
At that size?!
We're here for the queen. Focus on that.
I can't blame him for being shaken, though.
They seem to have limitless
potential for evolution.
And if there's an ant out there that
was born from an egg of that size...
Shit...
These bugs are tough.
One of them got my shoulder.
Want me to heal you?
Assuming you can afford it!
Quit screwing around, Shimizu. Just do it.
But there's something I want.
And it's not money this time.
More incoming...
Fine. What do you—